musically.com 2012-12-26

# Privacy | Music Ally

Music Ally takes the privacy of its users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing a personalised and valuable service. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at mail@musically.com

We do not send you any mailings that you have not requested, and you are able to opt out of all mailings at all times.

Signing up to this service does not result in unsolicited, junk or ‘spam’ mail nor does it result in adware or spyware.

Your credit card details are handled securely by our partner Worldpay and Music Ally cannot access them or misuse them.

We enable you to remain informed if any of these terms and conditions or privacy policies change. In the case that you no longer accept any revised conditions you will be able to unsubscribe from the service at no further cost.

### What data is collected

Music Ally is under certain legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with any data we collect on our users. We will collect the information fairly and let you know how we will use it.

The information that you provide about yourself to Music Ally will only be used for the effective administration of the Site and to communicate with you. This does not apply to third party sites. Music Ally will adhere to current UK legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.

From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself, on a voluntary basis (e.g. name, company name and email address etc) in order to receive or use services on our website. Music Ally will print your name and business name (where applicable) on each emailed report. This is to identify the recipient of each report and also as a polite way of reminding our users that each report is for the recipient’s use only. Music Ally also reserves the right to include other non-financial personal information at a later date to make the report more personal to you.

Music Ally does not keep any financial details at all. All credit / debit card details are stored by our financial partner Worldpay. No financial details can be accessed through the Music Ally site.

### How we use the data

At a later date we may offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys carried out by Music Ally to help our research into the types of service we offer.

We may use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified):

  * to build up marketing profiles
  * to aid strategic development
  * to manage our relationship with advertisers and to audit usage of the site

### With whom do we share the data?

We may analyse and disclose aggregate data, as set out in the section above, to advertisers and other reputable businesses but we will not include any identifying information about individual subscribers. We may disclose information to business partners and sponsors but will notify you if this is to happen and will only collect information for this purpose with your express consent.

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

Your financial transactions with Worldpay are secure and direct; Music Ally does not store any credit card information on this site and cannot therefore misuse your credit card details.

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information Music Ally holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Please address requests to mail@musically.com

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the Music Ally Site and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way. The Site contains links to third party content; Music Ally does not take responsibility for the privacy policy of these sites.

If Music Ally is sold the company is entitled to sell the data to the buyer.

### Cookies

A cookie is information that a Web site puts on your hard disk so that it can remember something about you at a later time.

We use cookies on the site solely for the purpose of logging you in or out of the site but not to specifically track your activity in any way. You can turn cookies off using your browser at any time but this may result in a loss of functionality.

### Security

Music Ally will take all reasonable steps to ensure the security of the data we hold. We will make our best endeavours to prevent loss or alteration to all data.
